SubText: NoRMITA.326
Come here quick.
Come here.
Huang Tai Tai, this is my daughter.
Come here, Lindo.
Come over here.
Come to Mama.
Don't keep Huang Tai Tai
waiting.
She looks like a brat.
She's usually very obedient.
She's just shy today.
She looks so skinny.
Don't go by her looks.
Look at that lucky face.
She'll give you many grandsons.
Come here! Come here!
Have Huang Tai Tai take
a closer look at you.
Stop stuffing yourself!
No girl should eat so fast.
Look at those dirty spots!
Who would want such a dirty
daughter-in-law?
Always be careful.
Otherwise when you go
to Huang Tai Tai's,
she will disapprove of you.
Remember...
when you see Huang Tai Tai,
act happy.
Really, you are very lucky.
The marriage ceremony has begun.
Bride and groom, pay respect
to each other.
Pay respect to the ancestors.
Be blessed with prosperity!
Be blessed with many sons!
I have prayed to the gods
many days for you,
so that you were not too ugly,
or too old.
I must have prayed too hard.
Ha! Scared you to death!
I am the husband.
I make all the decisions.
You sleep on the floor.
Do it! Do it now!
Where are my grandsons?
My son says...
you often refuse...
to sleep with him.
What kind of a wife are you?
You sleep on your side.
Where are my grandsons?
Huh?
My son says he's planted enough
seeds in you to fill a basket.
Plenty for ten thousand grandsons!
It's all your fault!
Always running around,
letting my son's seeds spill out.
From now on,
you lie in bed all day.
Lie down!
Until my grandson comes!
Do you hear me?
Disgusting little thing!
Close all the windows!
Feel this. I'm pregnant.
That's impossible.
It's yours!
What'd I tell you?
She's like this all the time.
What the hell's happening?
What's wrong?
Tell me quick!
It's so scary.
It's too terrible to say.
I had a bad dream.
Our ancestors came to me!
So angry!
They told me if Tyan-yu stays...
in this marriage,
he will die.
What's this bullshit?
What a stupid girl to have bad dreams!
The ancestors said...
if the matter is not settled immediately,
they will begin...
the cycle of destruction!
There are three signs, he said.
First, he has drawn a spot
on Tyan-yu's back.
And this spot will eat away
Tyan-yu's flesh.
Just as it ate away our ancestor's face.
Next, our ancestor touched my mouth.
Our ancestor said...
if I don't leave this marriage,
all my teeth will fall out.
But how could I leave this family
I love so much?
I live and die for this family.
Our ancestor also said
this girl here...
is Tyan-yu's true spiritual wife...
already growing his son!
It's true!
To prove it our ancestor planted
the seed in her womb.
Already ripe in one day.
Ah Ping! Come over here!
Come over here!
If you don't believe me,
ask the matchmaker.
Matchmaker, how could you?
How could you?
Well...
mistakes happen in Heaven.
The hell with this!
Get out!
All of you!
You're so lucky.
You don't have ears like mine.
You'll have a better life!
But listen carefully to what is calling.
Can you feel in your heart...
what I am saying?
Will you always keep it there?
You know...
after today...
I will never...
give you any more advice.
Stop looking!
Open the watermelon!
Dog fart!
Honored guests!
Thank you for coming.
I have persuaded the famous diva,
Miss Bai Yen,
to sing in honor of my son.
Let me have him.
Don't touch it!
Who's this?
This person is a whore.
Just like you.
My son!
Listen to that voice!
Strong...
like his father!
Look at you! Disgusting!
You make me sick!
Clean up this mess!
You hear me?
You are not my daughter.
If you have any self-respect,
you should kill yourself.
Your husband just died,
and you've become another man's concubine.
If you have any dignity,
leave right away.
Let your mother go to heaven in peace.
You are no longer her daughter.
Mama, don't leave.
An-Mei, Mama's leaving.
Respect your uncle
and your aunties.
Remember, be obedient!
Don't forget your Mama.
If you take this child away,
she will become like you.
Never able to face anyone.
Never able to lift her head.
You are going to ruin her whole life!
So you've come back already.
This is the daughter you wanted
permission to bring?
Yes. Her name is An-Mei.
Put this on.
Second Wife, this is too expensive
for a small child.
She is not worthy of it.
Who is she to say who is worthy?
A treasure like you,
needs precious pearls to
light up your face.
You may call me Big Mother.
Give them back. Hurry now.
If you don't thank Big Mother,
you will make me very angry.
Thank you Big Mother.
An-Mei, give me the necklace!
I know you don't want to.
But I will not have her buy you
for such a cheap price.
Why should you believe me?
I have become nothing.
A Fourth Wife!
A low-class concubine.
But An-Mei,
I was not always like this.
I was a First Wife.
Your father's only wife!
Never forget that!
You are a daughter of a First Wife.
You can't!
My daughter is with me.
Then send her away.
Or let her watch!
An-Mei, go to your nanny's room.
Please.
An-Mei, why are you here alone?
I've been looking for you everywhere.
Is that his smell?
Why did you bring me here?
Nanny told me.
She told me everything.
You went to West Lake Temple,
to make offerings in memory
of my father.
Wu Tsing saw you there.
Second Wife invited you over...
to play mah-jong.
That night,
Wu Tsing came to your room...
Give me back my son!
I stayed alive,
to keep my hope of seeing you again
one day.
So it's all true!
I brought you here to give you
a better life.
But now...
I know what I really have to do.
Mama! Wake up!
Hurry, wake up!
Mama?
Can you see?
Can you see I am no longer scared?
I am strong now.
I see clearly now...
what's true and what's false.
My mother's ghost will return...
in three days to settle scores.
That day will be the Lunar New Year.
All debts must be paid by then.
Or horrible tragedies will befall you.
Lord Buddha, forgive me.
Mama's gone to heaven.
Gone? Mama's dead?
When?
Four months ago.
She loved you very much.
I'm your sister.June.
Our little sister.
I've come to take our mother's place.
I've come to bring you her hopes...
Our sister.
Our family.